A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers, Financial Material, Vouchers, Subseries FV FA262
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial Material, 1893-1916; F; 184.73 Cubic Feet
  - Voucher Indexes, 1887-1916; FV 15
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 41001-43000, 1909 September 27-1910 March 22; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 162)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 43001-45000, 1910 March 24-October 1; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 163)
      Inside Book Plate - Stamped - Frank McLees and Bros.
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 45001-47000, 1910 October 1-1911 March 29; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is partially detached with cracking along joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 164)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 18800
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 47001-49000, 1911 March 29-September 29; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is cracking along joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 165)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 49001-51000, 1911 October 2-1912 February 29; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 166)
      Inside Book Plate - The DEUTZ Lithographing Co. No. 260
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 51001-53000, Location Unknown (Box 167)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 53001-55000, 1912 August 2-1913 January 8; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 168)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and Bros, No. 92121
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 55001-57000, 1913 January 9-June 2; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges and corners are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is missing with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 169)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 57001-59000, 1913 June 3-October 20; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is cracking along joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 170)
      Inside Book Plate - Wm. F. Albers Mfg. No. 20
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 59001-61000, 1913 October 21-1914 February 27; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is cracking along joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 171)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 61001-63000, 1914 February 27-July 8; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is cracking along joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 172)
      Inside Book Plate - Wm. F. Albers Mfg. No. 363
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 63001-65000, 1914 July 8-November 30; Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is detached. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 173)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 65001-67000, Location Unknown (Box 174)
    - Voucher Index, Series A - Check Record, 67001-69000, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is cracking along the joints. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 175)
      Inside Book Plate - Edward V. Brokaw and Bros, No. B. 9146
    - Voucher Index, Series B, 1901, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is partially detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 176)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15083, Year 1897
    - Voucher Index, Series B, 1902, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is partially detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 177)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15130, Year 1898
    - Voucher Index, Series B, 1903, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is partially detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 178)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 15115, Year 1898
    - Voucher Index, Series B, 1904, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is partially detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's are intact and secure. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 179)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22429, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series B, 1909, Areas of the board are worn and faded. Areas along the edges, corners and spine are worn, frayed and missing pieces. Spine is partially detached with crash exposed. Paste Downs and Flyleaf's binding and stitching are loose and separating along gutter. Pages and gutters are intact and secure. (Box 180)
      Inside Book Plate - The Burr Index Company, No. 22443, Year 1903
    - Voucher Index, Series Jr-H, Location Unknown (Box 181)